My name is Peppa
And this is my little brother George
This is Mummy Pig
This is Daddy Pig
I'm Peppa
[George's Friend]
Peppa and her friends are playing at the playground
Peppa, Suzy and Danny
are playing on the roundabout
Are you ready?
-Ready!
Okay, here we go
-Whee!
Faster, faster!
All right then
-Whee!
George is too little to play on the roundabout
He's on the swings instead
Rebecca's here
And she's brought her little brother Richard too
Hi, everyone!
-Hi!
Can I play on the roundabout too?
Hop on, Rebecca
This time we're going to spin really, really fast
Richard wants to hop on the roundabout too
If Richard gets on as well
then we won't be able to spin so fast
Richard can play with George instead
Richard
Do you want to go and play with George?
No
George has a dinosaur
Just like yours!
Let's go and see
George and Richard are about the same age
Richard wants to see George's dinosaur
Dinosaur!
George
Can you lend your dinosaur to Richard to play with?
No way
Richard
Can you lend your dinosaur to George to play with?
No way
George and Richard don't want to share their dinosaurs
George
It's much more fun when you share your toys
George is such a good little boy
Dinosaur!
George doesn't like sharing
Richard
Now it's your turn to let George hold the dinosaur
Richard doesn't like sharing either
Why are you two crying so loudly?
Every time George and Richard play together
they end up crying
They're too little, they don't know how to play with others yet
As the big sister
why don't you teach them how to play together?
No problem
We could teach them to build sandcastles
Good idea
Let's go to the sandpit
George and Richard love playing in the sand
George, Richard
Let's all build a sandcastle together today
First, fill the bucket with sand
Then you turn the bucket upside down
And gently pat it down
Now we lift up the bucket
It worked!
Richard made a sandcastle
And George made a sandcastle too!
See, playing together is fun
Oh no
This isn't going well
It's your little brother's fault
He just wrecked George's sandcastle
Your little brother wrecked my little brother's sandcastle first
Hey, hey
You two, as the big sisters
should be teaching Richard and George
how to get along and play together
That's right, we're the big sisters
And George and Richard are too little
to know how to play nicely with others
I have a good idea
George
What's your favorite thing to play at the playground?
The seesaw
George's favorite is the seesaw
Seesaw
Turns out it's hard to play seesaw alone
Richard wants to play seesaw too
Seesaw
Look
George and Richard are finally playing together
Seesaw
George likes Richard
And Richard really likes George too!
George and Richard both love playing together
-Seesaw...